Scenic Hudson, Inc. Administrative History Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- Storm King Mountain, 20; 1.33 linear feet Boxes: 107 - 110 Folders: 1066 - 1101
  - “Storm King Mountain Project A Case Study/Simulation in Environmental Studies (Folder 1077, Box 108)
  - Case Study Extra Materials (Folder 1078, Box 108)
  - Publications (Folder 1079, Box 108)
  - Maps (&Pictures, Prepared) (Folder 1080, Box 108)
  - Maps (a) (Folder 1081, Box 108)
  - Maps (b) (Folder 1082, Box 108)
  - Pictures (Folder 1083, Box 108)
  - Scenic Hudson News Bulletin 1965-1969 (Folder 1084, Box 108)
  - House of Representatives (1) (Folder 1085, Box 109)
  - House of Representatives (2) (Folder 1086, Box 109)
  - House of Representatives (3) (Folder 1087, Box 109)
  - House of Representatives (4) (Folder 1088, Box 109)
  - Students Papers (1) (Folder 1089, Box 109)
  - Student Papers (2) (Folder 1090, Box 109)
  - Regatta Project (Folder 1091, Box 109)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 1092, Box 109)
  - Bear/Storm King Hearing Clippings (Folder 1093, Box 109)
  - Clippings (1) (Folder 1094, Box 109)
  - Clippings (2) (Folder 1095, Box 109)
  - Diagrams (Folder 1096, Box 110)
  - Legal Documents (a) (Folder 1097, Box 110)
  - Legal Documents (b) (Folder 1098, Box 110)
  - Clippings (a) (Folder 1099, Box 110)
  - Clippings (b) (Folder 1100, Box 110)
  - Correspondence on House Hearings (Folder 1101, Box 110)
- Transportation, 21; 0.67 linear feet Boxes: 111 - 112 Folders: 1102 - 1121
  Documents pertaining to the impact roadways and transportation has on the Hudson Valley.
  - Planning (Folder 1102, Box 111)
  - General Correspondence (Folder 1103, Box 111)
  - Highway Laws (Folder 1104, Box 111)
  - Transportation Printed Material and Maps (Folder 1105, Box 111)
  - Transportation Project Report: Draft Environmental Impact Statement (Folder 1106, Box 111)
  - Transportation Clippings (Folder 1107, Box 111)
  - Transportation Correspondence (Folder 1108, Box 111)
  - Official Reports (Folder 1109, Box 111)
  - Beacon Arterial (Folder 1110, Box 112)
  - Clippings (a) (Folder 1111, Box 112)
  - Clippings (b) (Folder 1112, Box 112)
  - Newburgh Arterial Correspondence (Folder 1113, Box 112)
  - ewburgh Arterial Printed Material (Folder 1114, Box 112)
  - Hudson River Corridor Study (Folder 1115, Box 112)
  - New York Transportation Council (Folder 1116, Box 112)
  - Metro North Correspondence (Folder 1117, Box 112)
  - Metro North Clippings, Photos, and Maps (Folder 1118, Box 112)
  - Metro North- Background and Research (Folder 1119, Box 112)
  - Tappan Zee Bridge (Folder 1120, Box 112)
  - Billboards on the West Side Highway (Folder 1121, Box 112)
- Wallace Fund, 1985-1998; 22; 5.33 linear feet Boxes: 113 - 128 Folders: 1122 - 1254
  Information, documents, minutes, and financial materials concerning Scenic Hudson’s involvement with that Wallace Fund.
  - Attorney General Investigation (1) (Folder 1122, Box 113)
  - Attorney General Investigation (2) (Folder 1123, Box 113)
  - Attorney General Investigation (3) (Folder 1124, Box 113)
  - Attorney General Investigation (4) (Folder 1125, Box 113)
  - Attorney General Investigation (5) (Folder 1126, Box 113)
  - Canterbury Ranch Correspondence (Folder 1127, Box 113)
  - Canterbury Ranch Printed Material (Folder 1128, Box 113)
  - Correspondence 1989 (Folder 1129, Box 114)
  - Correspondence 1990 (Folder 1130, Box 114)
  - Correspondence 1991 (Folder 1131, Box 114)
  - Correspondence 1992 (Folder 1132, Box 114)
  - Correspondence 1993 (Folder 1133, Box 114)
  - Open Space Institute Correspondence (Folder 1134, Box 114)
  - Common Stock Correspondence (Folder 1135, Box 114)
  - Hubbard and Perkins Property Correspondence (Folder 1136, Box 114)
  - Mystery Point Correspondence (Folder 1137, Box 114)
  - Reader’s Digest Correspondence (Folder 1138, Box 114)
  - Misc. Correspondence (Folder 1139, Box 114)
  - Correspondence to Scenic Hudson and the Open Space Institute (Folder 1140, Box 115)
  - Simpson, Thatcher, and Bartlett Correspondence (Folder 1141, Box 115)
  - Simpson, Thatcher, and Bartlett Correspondence (Folder 1142, Box 115)
  - Franny Reese Financial Files (Folder 1143, Box 116)
  - Financial (Folder 1144, Box 116)
  - Fund Issues (Folder 1145, Box 116)
  - Fund Issues (Folder 1146, Box 116)
  - Fund Issues (Folder 1147, Box 116)
  - Investment Report Summary 1990 (Folder 1148, Box 117)
  - Investment Program (Folder 1149, Box 117)
  - Investment Performance as of Dec. 31, 1992 (Folder 1150, Box 117)
  - Reader’s Digest Stock (Folder 1151, Box 117)
  - Financial Report June 24, 1991 (Folder 1152, Box 117)
  - Investment Recommendations October 28, 1991 (Folder 1153, Box 117)
  - Investment Report October 21, 1993 (Folder 1154, Box 117)
  - Investment Update March 3, 1994 (Folder 1155, Box 117)
  - Investment Report July 16, 1993 (Folder 1156, Box 117)
  - Proposal of Bonds Feb. 22, 1991 (Folder 1157, Box 117)
  - Trust Article (Folder 1158, Box 117)
  - Financial Issues Concerning Open Space Institute (Folder 1159, Box 117)
  - Institutional Transformational Fund (Folder 1160, Box 117)
  - Analysis of Traces offering (Folder 1161, Box 117)
  - Financial Statements and Budgets 1990-1991 (Folder 1162, Box 118)
  - 1991 Expenses (Folder 1163, Box 118)
  - Fund Planning 1991-1992 (Folder 1164, Box 118)
  - Financial Statements June 30, 1992 and 1992 (Folder 1165, Box 118)
  - Financial Issues 1992 (Folder 1166, Box 118)
  - Financial Issues May 3, 1993 (Folder 1167, Box 118)
  - Approval for Budget 1994 (Folder 1168, Box 118)
  - Investment Update August 30, 1994 (Folder 1169, Box 118)
  - Investment Report July 1994 (Folder 1170, Box 118)
  - 1995 Budget Proposal (Folder 1171, Box 118)
  - HHF Board of Trustees (Folder 1172, Box 119)
  - HHF Board of Trustees Correspondence (Folder 1173, Box 119)
  - By-Laws and Trustees (Folder 1174, Box 119)
  - Certificate of Incorporation (Folder 1175, Box 119)
  - Directors 1991 (Folder 1176, Box 119)
  - General Information about Scenic Hudson and Fund (Folder 1177, Box 119)
  - Scenic Hudson Land Trust Committee (Folder 1178, Box 119)
  - Legal Issues (Folder 1179, Box 120)
  - Legal Issues (Folder 1180, Box 120)
  - Christine DeVita, Esq. Miscellaneous (Folder 1181, Box 120)
  - Roberts and Holland (Folder 1182, Box 120)
  - Jerry McCoy (Folder 1183, Box 120)
  - Confidentiality Agreements (Folder 1184, Box 121)
  - Assurance of Discontinuance Pursuant to Executive Law (Folder 1185, Box 121)
  - Executed Endowment and Coordination Agreements (Folder 1186, Box 121)
  - Miscellaneous Legal Issues (Folder 1187, Box 121)
  - Legal Issues (Folder 1188, Box 121)
  - Legal Issues (Folder 1189, Box 121)
  - Meeting Nov. 28, 1985 (Folder 1190, Box 122)
  - Meeting Dec. 19, 1985 (Folder 1191, Box 122)
  - Meeting Dec. 2, 1986 (Folder 1192, Box 122)
  - Meeting Dec. 9, 1987 (Folder 1193, Box 122)
  - Meeting Nov. 1988 (Folder 1194, Box 122)
  - Meeting Nov. 30, 1989 (Folder 1195, Box 122)
  - Meeting March 5, 1990 (Folder 1196, Box 122)
  - Meeting Sept. 26, 1990 (Folder 1197, Box 122)
  - Meeting Dec. 3, 1990 (Folder 1198, Box 122)
  - Meeting Dec. 12, 1990 (Folder 1199, Box 122)
  - Meetings Feb. and May 1991 (Folder 1200, Box 123)
  - Meeting June 24, 1991 (Folder 1201, Box 123)
  - Meeting July 18, 1991 (Folder 1202, Box 123)
  - Meeting Dec. 3, 1991 (Folder 1203, Box 123)
  - Meeting April 14, 1992 (Folder 1204, Box 123)
  - Meeting April 14, 1992 (Folder 1205, Box 123)
  - Meeting Nov. 10, 1992 (Folder 1206, Box 123)
  - Meeting Nov. 10, 1992 (Folder 1207, Box 123)
  - Meeting Dec. 1, 1992 (Folder 1208, Box 123)
  - Meeting Jan. 25, 1993 (Folder 1209, Box 124)
  - Meeting April 19, 1993 (Folder 1210, Box 124)
  - Meeting April 19, 1993 (Folder 1211, Box 124)
  - Meeting June 10, 1993 (Folder 1212, Box 124)
  - Meeting Dec. 13, 1993 (Folder 1213, Box 124)
  - Meeting Dec. 13, 1993 (Folder 1214, Box 124)
  - Meeting April 20, 1994 (Folder 1215, Box 125)
  - Meeting Sept. 26, 1994 (Folder 1216, Box 125)
  - Meeting Dec. 15, 1994 (Folder 1217, Box 125)
  - HHF meeting Oct. 28, 1998 (Folder 1218, Box 125)
  - Outstanding Issues Meeting 2001 (Folder 1219, Box 125)
  - American Dreamers (Folder 1220, Box 126)
  - Board of Trustees (Folder 1221, Box 126)
  - Carolyn Clark (Folder 1222, Box 126)
  - Current HHF Matters (Folder 1223, Box 126)
  - Current HHF Matters (Folder 1224, Box 126)
  - Executive Director (Folder 1225, Box 126)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 1226, Box 126)
  - News Articles (Folder 1227, Box 126)
  - Carolyn Osteen (Folder 1228, Box 126)
  - Public Support Test (Folder 1229, Box 126)
  - Reader’s Digest (Folder 1230, Box 126)
  - Section 509 of the IRS (Folder 1231, Box 126)
  - Special Committee Info (Folder 1232, Box 126)
  - Project Hillside (Folder 1233, Box 127)
  - Swinburn Project (Folder 1234, Box 127)
  - Papscanee Island (Folder 1235, Box 127)
  - Sterling Forest (Folder 1236, Box 127)
  - Project Updates (Folder 1237, Box 127)
  - Esopus Meadows (Folder 1238, Box 127)
  - Easements (Folder 1239, Box 127)
  - Malcolm Gordon School (Folder 1240, Box 127)
  - Olana View Shed (Folder 1241, Box 127)
  - Working Group Project 1991 (Folder 1242, Box 128)
  - Staff Report on Custodian and Cash Management Issues Oct. 7, 1992 (Folder 1243, Box 128)
  - Report from Scenic Hudson 1992 (Folder 1244, Box 128)
  - Annual Reports 1992 (Folder 1245, Box 128)
  - Annual Report 1985 (Folder 1246, Box 128)
  - Report 1992 (Folder 1247, Box 128)
  - Report 1993 (Folder 1248, Box 128)
  - Report 1994 (Folder 1249, Box 128)
  - Land Proposals (Folder 1250, Box 128)
  - Project Proposals Sept. 1994 (Folder 1251, Box 128)
  - Land Project Proposals April 1994 (Folder 1252, Box 128)
  - Proposal by the Open Space Institute (Folder 1253, Box 128)
  - Spider Falls Request for Funding (Folder 1254, Box 128)
- West Meets East, 23; 0.33 linear feet Box: 129 Folders: 1255 - 1263
  Information concerning a water saving strategy for the twentieth century.
  - Corporations Correspondence (Folder 1255, Box 129)
  - Speakers Correspondence (Folder 1256, Box 129)
  - Endorsement Replies (Folder 1257, Box 129)
  - Endorsing Organizations Material (Folder 1258, Box 129)
  - Advisory Committee Correspondence (Folder 1259, Box 129)
  - WRS Steering Committee Correspondence (Board) (Folder 1260, Box 129)
  - Water Resources Symposium (Folder 1261, Box 129)
  - WRS Originals (Folder 1262, Box 129)
  - Printed Material (Folder 1263, Box 129)
- Environmental Studies, 24; 3.67 linear feet Boxes: 130 - 145 Folders: 1264 - 1394
  Environmental studies used, wrote, and/or conducted by Scenic Hudson, Inc. Various studies include: air pollution, coastal management, fish studies, etc.
  Series is divided into eight subseries, subseries are arranged alphabetically by subject
  - General Information, 24.1
    General Information; Specific Site Studies H - Z
    - Alton Dam (Folder 1264, Box 130)
    - Appalachian Trail correspondence (Folder 1265, Box 130)
    - Appalachian Trail publications, clippings, participants (Folder 1266, Box 130)
    - Appalachian Trail proposals (Folder 1267, Box 130)
    - Baldwin Hills Reservoir (Folder 1268, Box 130)
    - Construction Work in Progress (Folder 1269, Box 130)
    - Cooling towers (Folder 1270, Box 130)
    - Council on the Environment of NYC (Folder 1271, Box 130)
    - Dam Failures (Folder 1272, Box 130)
    - Environmental Action (Folder 1273, Box 130)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Case (Folder 1274, Box 130)
    - Environmental Protection Agency General Correspondence (Folder 1275, Box 130)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Hearings Correspondence (Folder 1276, Box 130)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Hearings Information (Folder 1277, Box 130)
    - Environmental Study Conference Bulletins (Folder 1278, Box 130)
    - General Correspondence (Folder 1279, Box 130)
    - Hastings Land Fill (Folder 1280, Box 130)
    - Hudson River Investigations Evaluation of Proposed Pumped Storage Plant Related to fish (Folder 1281, Box 130)
    - Hudson Flood Skimming Project News (Folder 1282, Box 131)
    - Hudson Flood Skimming Project Clippings (Folder 1283, Box 131)
    - Hudson Flood Skimming Project Reports (Folder 1284, Box 131)
    - Hudson Flood Skimming Project Miscellaneous (Folder 1285, Box 131)
    - Hudson Flood Skimming Project Correspondence (Folder 1286, Box 131)
    - Hudson River Basin Study (Folder 1287, Box 131)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council Budget (Folder 1288, Box 131)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council correspondence (Folder 1289, Box 131)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council Printed Material and Clippings (Folder 1290, Box 131)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council Publications and Newsletters (Folder 1291, Box 131)
    - NY Environmental News (Folder 1292, Box 131)
    - Outdoor Life Conservation Award (Folder 1293, Box 131)
    - Publications (Folder 1294, Box 131)
    - Striped Bass Printed Material (Folder 1295, Box 131)
    - Water Pollution (Folder 1296, Box 131)
    - Wetlands and Fish (Folder 1297, Box 131)
  - Air Pollution, 24.2
    Clippings, reports, correspondence, statements
    - NY Times clippings 1965-1966 (Folder 1298, Box 132)
    - NY Times Clippings 1967 (Folder 1299, Box 132)
    - Clippings: Herald Tribune (Folder 1300, Box 132)
    - Clippings: Evening news, L.I. Press, Times Herald Record, Christian Science Monitor (Folder 1301, Box 132)
    - Clippings: Daily News, Newsday, NY Post, and Sunday News (Folder 1302, Box 132)
    - Clippings: Chicago Tribune and Washington Post (Folder 1303, Box 132)
    - Clippings: Wall Street Journal, World Tribune Journal, and Journal of Commerce (Folder 1304, Box 132)
    - Clippings: Austin Heller, commissioner of Air Pollution control (Folder 1305, Box 132)
    - Clippings: miscellaneous (Folder 1306, Box 132)
    - Citizens for Clean air Annual Reports (Folder 1307, Box 133)
    - Citizens for Clean Air correspondence (Folder 1308, Box 133)
    - Citizens for Clean Air Press Releases and news clippings (Folder 1309, Box 133)
    - Austin Heller Correspondence (Folder 1310, Box 133)
    - General Correspondence (Folder 1311, Box 133)
    - Statements (Folder 1312, Box 133)
  - Coastal Management, 24.3
    Correspondence, legal papers, printed materials, publications
    - Correspondence (Folder 1313, Box 134)
    - Legal Papers (Folder 1314, Box 134)
    - Preliminaries (Folder 1315, Box 134)
    - Printed Material (Folder 1316, Box 134)
    - Publications (Folder 1317, Box 134)
    - State Dept. Papers (Folder 1318, Box 134)
  - Fish Fights, 1965-1973; 24.4
    Correspondence, legal documents, media, photographs, printed materials, reports, Clippings
    - Correspondence 1965 (Folder 1319, Box 135)
    - Correspondence 1966-1967 (Folder 1320, Box 135)
    - Correspondence 1968-1969 (Folder 1321, Box 135)
    - Correspondence 1970-1972 (Folder 1322, Box 135)
    - Legal Documents (Folder 1323, Box 135)
    - Media Files (Folder 1324, Box 135)
    - Photographs (Folder 1325, Box 135)
    - Printed Materials (Folder 1326, Box 135)
    - Reports (Folder 1327, Box 135)
    - Clippings 1965-1966 (Folder 1328, Box 136)
    - Clippings 1967-1969 (Folder 1329, Box 136)
    - Clippings 1970 (Folder 1330, Box 136)
    - Clippings 1971 (Folder 1331, Box 136)
    - Clippings 1972-1973 and miscellaneous (Folder 1332, Box 136)
  - Fish Studies & the Fisherman’s Association, 24.5
    Investigations, legal documents, reports, media, general information; Binders of fish studies; Fisheries, water pollution, conferences, clippings
    - Erie Investigation (Folder 1333, Box 137)
    - Legal Documents (Folder 1334, Box 137)
    - Printed Material and clippings (Folder 1335, Box 137)
    - Reports (Folder 1336, Box 137)
    - Reports: impact on Fisheries (Folder 1337, Box 137)
    - Sport Fishing (Folder 1338, Box 137)
    - Fisherman’s Association correspondence (Folder 1339, Box 137)
    - Fisherman’s Association general information (Folder 1340, Box 137)
    - Binder of Fish studies (Folder 1341, Box 138)
    - Binder of fish studies by the Hudson River Policy Committee (Folder 1342, Box 138)
    - Binder of Fish studies (Folder 1343, Box 138)
    - Stony brook Fish (Folder 1344, Box 139)
    - Stony Brook Conference: Power Generation and the Aquatic Environment 1977 (Folder 1345, Box 139)
    - Fish 1977 (Folder 1346, Box 139)
    - Fisheries 1978-1979: notes on Hearings (Folder 1347, Box 139)
    - Fish/Fishing clippings, correspondence, and articles (Folder 1348, Box 139)
    - Raney Report regarding Striped Bass (Folder 1349, Box 139)
    - Fish Hearing: Washington D.C. (Folder 1350, Box 139)
    - Hudson River Fisheries (Folder 1351, Box 139)
    - Hudson River Fisherman’s Association (Folder 1352, Box 139)
    - Nassau Fish and Game 02/11/1965: Biologist Dave Wallace Statement (Folder 1353, Box 139)
    - Water Pollution Conference 1965 (Folder 1354, Box 139)
    - Fish Articles and Clippings (Folder 1355, Box 139)
    - Striped Bass (Folder 1356, Box 139)
  - Hudson River Study Act, 24.6
    Clippings, correspondence, legal materials, printed materials
    - Clippings (Folder 1357, Box 140)
    - Correspondence 1977 (Folder 1358, Box 140)
    - Correspondence Jan.-April 1978 (Folder 1359, Box 140)
    - Correspondence May 1978 (Folder 1360, Box 140)
    - Correspondence June 1978-July 1979 (Folder 1361, Box 140)
    - Endorsees (Folder 1362, Box 140)
    - Legal Materials (Folder 1363, Box 140)
    - Legal Materials (Folder 1364, Box 140)
    - Printed Material (Folder 1365, Box 140)
    - Clippings (Folder 1357, Box 140)
    - Correspondence 1977 (Folder 1358, Box 140)
    - Correspondence Jan.-April 1978 (Folder 1359, Box 140)
    - Correspondence May 1978 (Folder 1360, Box 140)
    - Correspondence June 1978-July 1979 (Folder 1361, Box 140)
    - Endorsees (Folder 1362, Box 140)
    - Legal Materials (Folder 1363, Box 140)
    - Legal Materials (Folder 1364, Box 140)
    - Printed Material (Folder 1365, Box 140)
  - Reports, 1971-1983; 24.7
    Reports on Beacon, Transportation; Environmental Impact Statements; Miscellaneous Reports
    - Beacon Arterial Sept. 1971 (Folder 1366, Box 141)
    - Transportation Nov. 1979 (Folder 1367, Box 141)
    - Transportation June 1982 (Folder 1368, Box 141)
    - Transportation Oct. 1982 (Folder 1369, Box 141)
    - Transportation June 1983 (Folder 1370, Box 141)
    - Transportation Feb. 1984 (Folder 1371, Box 141)
    - Miscellaneous reports (Folder 1372, Box 141)
    - Miscellaneous reports (Folder 1373, Box 141)
    - General correspondence (Folder 1374, Box 141)
    - Hudson River East Bank Natural Areas, Clermont to Norrie (Folder 1375, Box 142)
    - Draft Environmental Impact Statement: Bridgeview Jan. 1983 (Folder 1376, Box 142)
    - Final Environmental Impact Statement: Bridgeview July 1983 (Folder 1377, Box 142)
    - Draft Environmental Impact Statement: octane Petroleum Recovery and Finishing Facility (Folder 1378, Box 142)
    - Draft Environmental Impact Statement: octane Petroleum Recovery and Finishing Facility Volume I (Folder 1379, Box 142)
    - Draft Environmental Impact Statement: octane Petroleum Recovery and Finishing Facility Volume II (Folder 1380, Box 142)
    - Coal Export Facilities in Ulster county Environmental Assessment Report (Folder 1381, Box 143)
    - Draft Environmental Impact Statement for the River Village Mobile Home Park in the Town of Fishkill (Folder 1382, Box 143)
    - Oil Storage Facilities Study Kingston, NY (Folder 1383, Box 143)
    - Final Environmental Impact Statement Village of Nyack Waterfront Development (Folder 1384, Box 143)
    - Updating the Urban Renewal Plan for the Beacon Urban Renewal Project No. 1 (Folder 1385, Box 143)
    - Town of Hyde Park Local Waterfront Revitalization Program (Folder 1386, Box 143)
  - Oversized & Legal Size, 24.8
    Legal and Oversized documents
    - Air Pollution: Mayor Lindsay (File 1387, Box 144)
    - Environmental Planning Lobby Correspondence (File 1388, Box 144)
    - Environmental Planning Lobby Minutes (File 1389, Box 144)
    - Environmental Planning Lobby Newsletters (File 1390, Box 144)
    - Hudson flood Skimming Project: Legal Papers (File 1391, Box 144)
    - Hudson River Study Act: Clippings and Press Releases (File 1392, Box 144)
    - Hugh Carey (File 1393, Box 144)
    - Binder for the Draft Environmental Impact Statement for IBM Data Systems Division’s North 100 Site (File 1394, Box 145)
- Exhibits, 25; 0.67 linear feet Boxes: 146 - 147 Folders: 1395 - 1419
  Exhibits used in court proceedings.
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 1395, Box 146)
  - Frenchy’s Color Lab (Folder 1396, Box 146)
  - General (Folder 1397, Box 146)
  - Correspondence, Dec. 1977-May 1978 (Folder 1398, Box 146)
  - Correspondence, June 1978-March 1980 (Folder 1399, Box 146)
  - Insurance Correspondence (Folder 1400, Box 146)
  - American Museum of Natural History Correspondence (Folder 1401, Box 146)
  - Ted Spiegel (Folder 1402, Box 146)
  - Clippings and Press Releases (Folder 1403, Box 146)
  - Publications (Folder 1404, Box 146)
  - Poughkeespie (Folder 1405, Box 146)
  - The New Response: General (Folder 1406, Box 147)
  - The New Response: Notes (Folder 1407, Box 147)
  - The New Response: Clippings and Press Releases (Folder 1408, Box 147)
  - The New Response: Correspondence @ Albany (Folder 1409, Box 147)
  - The New Response: Correspondence @ Vassar (Folder 1410, Box 147)
  - The New Response: Correspondence @ New York (Folder 1411, Box 147)
  - The New Response: Printed Material (Folder 1412, Box 147)
  - The New Response: Contributions (Folder 1413, Box 147)
  - American Legacy: General (Folder 1414, Box 147)
  - American Legacy: Printed Material (Folder 1415, Box 147)
  - American Legacy: Bios (Folder 1416, Box 147)
  - American Legacy: Correspondence (Folder 1417, Box 147)
  - American Legacy: Press Releases and Clippings (Folder 1418, Box 147)
  - American Legacy: Slide #0119 (Folder 1419, Box 147)
- Clippings, 1959-2000; 26; 7.25 linear feet Boxes: 148 - 168 Folders: 1420 - 1639
  Newspaper clippings and articles relating to cases and events of interest on by Scenic Hudson, Inc.
  - 1959 (Folder 1420, Box 148)
  - 1963-1964 (Folder 1421, Box 148)
  - SHPC Paste up of News Clips; 1964 (Folder 1422, Box 148)
  - Clippings re: “Shape up the Hudson” Regatta; 1964 (Folder 1423, Box 148)
  - SHPC Paste up of News Clips; 1965 (Folder 1424, Box 148)
  - 1965 (Folder 1425, Box 148)
  - 1965 (including “Outdoor Life” article) (Folder 1426, Box 148)
  - “Back Hudson Bill” 1965 (Folder 1427, Box 148)
  - SHPC Paste up of News Clips; 1966 (Folder 1428, Box 148)
  - 1966-1970 (Folder 1429, Box 148)
  - Newspaper; “Conservation Council Comments” 1969 (Folder 1430, Box 148)
  - 1971 (Folder 1431, Box 148)
  - 1973-1975 (Folder 1432, Box 148)
  - Newspaper; “Suffolk Outdoors” January 1973&May 1973 (Folder 1433, Box 148)
  - 1976 (Folder 1434, Box 148)
  - Hudson Valley Project, October 1964 (Folder 1435, Box 149)
  - Hudson Valley Project, November 1964 (Folder 1436, Box 149)
  - Hudson Valley Project, December 1964 (Folder 1437, Box 149)
  - Stewart Airport, Jan.-July 2000 (Folder 1438, Box 150)
  - Stewart Airport, July-Dec. 2000 (Folder 1439, Box 150)
  - General Electric, 1999-2000 (Folder 1440, Box 150)
  - General Electric, Nov.-Dec. 2000 (Folder 1441, Box 150)
  - General Electric Ads, 2000 (Folder 1442, Box 150)
  - Scenic Hudson, Nov.-Dec. 1999 (Folder 1443, Box 151)
  - Scenic Hudson, January 2000 (Folder 1444, Box 151)
  - Scenic Hudson, February 2000 (Folder 1445, Box 151)
  - Scenic Hudson, March 2000 (Folder 1446, Box 151)
  - Scenic Hudson, April 2000 (Folder 1447, Box 151)
  - Scenic Hudson, May 2000 (Folder 1448, Box 151)
  - Scenic Hudson, June 2000 (Folder 1449, Box 151)
  - Scenic Hudson, July 2000 (Folder 1450, Box 151)
  - Scenic Hudson, August 2000 (Folder 1451, Box 151)